Guide to the John Tabor Kempe Papers 1678-1782 (bulk 1752-1774) MS 344
New-York Historical Society
- Series 1: Court Case Records, 1678-1778 (bulk 1752-1774), and Undated, 1678-1778 and Undated
  - Subseries 2: Supreme Court of Judicature, Civil
    - Patrick and Elizabeth Coyne [Coine] vs. John Meyers [Meyer]: Trespass and slander, 1759 (Box 3, Folder 1)
      Case includes memo for action, demurrer, notes, declaration, joinder in demurrer, and notes on slander.
    - John Cross, David Crosse, Peter Blackburn, Robert Barclay, and John Crosse vs. Robert Sinclair: Trespass, 1773-1774 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Narratio also says New York Mayor's Court on front and Supreme Court on abstract. Special bail field with the Chief Justice. Case includes narratio, notice of bail, and costs.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Abraham Cuyler and others vs. Benjamin Westervelt: Ejectment, 1770-1771 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Trial in Dutchess County and New York City. First heard in Council [one item]. See also correspondence between John Tabor Kempe and Hermanus Schuyler, Sherrif of Albany. See letter from John Tabor Kempe to Cadwallader Colden dated 8 March, 1762.
    - Abraham Cuyler and George McBeath vs. Beamsly Glazier, 1771-1773 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      See also the following correspondence: John Tabor Kempe to William Smith, 13 January, 1771; John Tabor Kempe to Beamsly Glazier, 16 January, 1772; Beamsly Glazier to John Tabor Kempe, 25 June, 1771; Isaac Todd to Beamsly Glazier, 27 April, 1771. Case includes affidavits, warrant of attorney (draft), notices, bond, release of actions, notice of bail, costs, and a statement of case.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Henry Cuyler, Abraham Cuyler, John Van Cortlandt, Isaac Low, and Cornelius Cuyler vs. [John Stiles] Thomas Jaycocks: Ejectment, 1773-1774 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Trial in Dutchess County. Case includes declaration, notice of trial, countermand notice of trial, common rule, and plea.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Henry Cuyler, Abraham Cuyler, John Van Cortlandt, Isaac Low, Cornelius Cuyler vs. [John Stiles] Francis Jaycocks and John Van Cortlandt: Ejectment, 1774 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      Trial in Dutchess County. See letters from John Tabor Kempe to Tuenis Tappen, dated 27 May, 1774 and 31 May, 1774. See also correspondence bewtween Jacobus Swartwout and John Tabor Kempe. Case includes costs, directions, rule, narratio, notice of trial, notices, venire, and countermand notice of trial.
    - Ebenezer Dayton vs. Henry Parsons, Jeremiah Hedges the Younger, Ananias Mulford, Barnabas Mulford, Samuel Russell, Stephen Russell, Jeremiah Conckling, Ezekiel Mulford, Abraham Gardiner, David Fithen, Lewis Chatfield, Daniel Dayton, Jacob Conkling, Henry Chatfield: Trespass, 1772-1773 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Trial in Suffolk County. See George Muirson to John Tabor Kempe dated 28 July, 1772. Case includes narratio, notes, list of persons involved, brief, notice of trial, trial notes, plea, and affidavits.
    - Jane Dew vs. Jonathan Hampton: Debt, 1775 (Box 3, Folder 3)
      Case includes brief.
    - [John Denne] Anne De Lancey and Lewis Johnston vs. Benjamin Carnell: Ejectment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - James De Lancey [Delancey] and John L. Johnston vs. John Hunt, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Oliver De Lancey [Delancey], John Watts, John Van Cortlandt, Willoughby Bertie, Charlotte Bertie, Charles Fitzroy, Ann Fitzroy, William Skinner, Susannah Skinner, Jacobus Ver Planck, John Ver Planck, and Philip Ver Planck vs. [John Stiles] Benjamin Jaycocks [Jacoks]: Ejectment, 1773 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Trial in Dutchess County. Case includes common rule, notes, and narratio.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Oliver De Lancey [Delancey], John Watts, John Van Cortlandt, Willoughby Bertie, Charlotte Bertie, Charles Fitzroy, Ann Fitzroy, William Skinner, Susannah Skinner, Jacobus Ver Planck, John Ver Planck, and Philip Ver Planck vs. [John Stiles] John Jaycocks: Ejectment, 1774 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Trial in Dutchess County. Case includes common rule, notice of trial, countermand of notice of trial, and panel of jurors.
    - Stephen De Lancey vs. Abraham Yates Jr.: Debt, 1773 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      See correspondence between John Tabor Kempe and Abraham Yates, Jr. Case includes plea and narratio.
    - Isaac De Lyon [Delyon] vs. Richard Hitchens [Hitchings], 1772-1773 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      See correspondence from Isaac Delyon to John Tabor Kempe, dated 17 March, 1773.
    - George Deree vs. The Trustees of Brookhaven, 1772-1773 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Case includes motion to quash proceedings and exceptions. Cannot confirm countersuit.
    - James Dillon vs. Isaac Sears: Debt, 1758-1760 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      See also correspondence from John Tabor Kempe to Issac Sears, dated 17 October, 1759; James Dillon to John Tabor Kempe dated 31 December, 1759. Trial is in regards to French Indian War vessels and the privateer Belle Isle. Case includes acquittance, petition, declaration, and costs.
    - Jonas Philips and trustees and creditors of Thomas Dods [Dodds], an absconding debtor vs. Alexander Robinson: Debt, 1767-1769 (Box 3, Folder 4)
      Filed under Dods. Case includes notes on trial, brief, affidavits, and costs.
    - Medcalf [Medcef] [Metcalf] Eden vs. William Davis, 1774 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      Case includes notes on the trial and brief.
    - Robert Ewing vs. Robert McGinnis, Henry Van Schaack, and William Cairns: Trespass and fraud, 1762-1768 (Box 3, Folder 5)
      See also a letter from John Pratt dated 1 April, 1766 and Henry Van Schaack to John Tabor Kempe, 12 October, 1765. Case includes notice of trial, affidavit, brief, affidavit to show cause, notice of trial, narratio, notice of special bail, countermand of notice of trial, notice of examining witnesses, depostions, and costs.
    - William Faulkner vs. Garret Rapalje: Trespass and slander, 1771-1772 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      See also Garret Rapalje vs. William Faulkner, Supreme Court of Judicature. Case includes note, brief, declaration, narratio, notes of testimony, affidavits, plea, notice of trial, list of panel, writ, and costs.
    - George Folliott [Foliot] [Foliott] vs. Henry Hartley: Trespass, 1762-1764 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Case includes a statement of case, affidavit, notice of bail, petition, notice of exception to bail, narratio, and plea.
    - George Folliott vs. Richard Morris, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Case includes notes and brief.
    - Thomas Forsey vs. Waddel Cunningham: Assault, 1764 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      Case includes writ.
    - Philip Francis and Joseph Dean vs. Isaac De Lyon [Delyon] and Joseph Abrahams: Debt, 1773 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Four interrelated cases, filed together: Philip Francis v. Isaac De Lyon, Joseph Dean v. Isaac De Lyon, Philip Francis v. Joseph Abrahams, Joseph Dean v. Joseph Abrahams. Many documents combine the cases. See also correspondence from John Tabor Kempe to Francis and Dean dated 29 July, 1773. Case includes plea, oyer, narratio (draft), copy letter of license,accounts, notices, certificates, affidavits, oyer, plea, memoranda, and costs.
    - Thomas Franklin, Jr. and James Franklin vs. Daniel Dunscomb and Abraham Cock, 1762 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      See correspondence from John Tabor Kempe to Beverly Robinson dated 21 February, 1763.
    - Michael Furey vs. William Wilson [Willson]: Trespass, 1764-1765 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      Case includes affidavits, petition and order for bail, notes, exception to bail, writ, declaration, narratio, and notice of special bail.
    - George Graham and Robert Kain vs. James Burne [Burn] and George Burne [Burn]: Debt, 1765 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Trial in Ulster County. Case includes narratio, writ of venditioni exponas, and judgement roll.
    - Joseph Green vs. John Cooper: Trespass, 1770-1771 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Trial in Dutchess County. See correspondence from John Cooper to John Tabor Kempe and William Humfrey to John Tabor Kempe dated 5 August, 1771. Case includes record, notes, memo of action, affidavit, and certiorari.
    - [Griffiths and Thomas] [Anthony Kendall] vs. Joseph Forman: Debt, 1767-1768 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Joseph Forman was an insolvant debtor and was arrested at the suit of Anthony Kendall, creditor. Case includes list of creditors, petition, and affidavit.
    - Abraham Haasbrook Jr. vs. William Kelly, 1768 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Case includes ruling and statement of case.
    - Samuel Hake vs. Philip Skene: Debt, 1774 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Trial in Charlotte County and includes notes.
    - Robert Hannas vs. Michael De Voe: Assault, battery, and slander, 1763-1764 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      See correspondence between Robert Hannas and John Tabor Kempe. See also letter from Abraham Low to John Tabor Kempe, dated 8 October, 1763. Case includes writs, notes, affidavits, notes of evidence, notes of slander, and declarations.
    - William Haviland vs. Samuel Elwell, 1753 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Case includes petition to move case to the Supreme Court.
    - Barrak [Barack] [Barak] Hays vs. Solomon Simson [Simpson]: Trespass, assault, and battery, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Filed with Hays vs. Seixas in Supreme Court of Judicature. Case includes notice of trial, narratio, writ, plea, replication, brief, and trial notes.
    - Barrak [Barack] [Barak] Hays vs. Benjamin Seixas: Trespass, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 2)
      Case is filed with Hays vs. Simson in Supreme Court of Judicature. Case includes notice of trial, narratio, replication, and trial notes.
    - Abel Hardenbrook vs. John Bogert Jr. and others, 1765-1766 (Box 4, Folder 3)
      See letter from John Tabor Kempe to James Duane, dated 28 June, 1766. Case includes argument for plaintiff, statement of case, trial notes, opinion, and notes.
    - Robert Henry, James Abbott, and John Farrell [Farrel] vs. Benjamin Roberts, 1770-1774 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Case includes notes, habeas corpus to remove suit to Supreme Court Judicature, memos, affidavits, notices, certiorari, costs, cross exam, brief, narratio, and trial notes.
    - Thomas Hicks vs. John Talman [Tallman] [Taulman]: Trespass, 1760-1762 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      See also The King vs. Thomas Hicks [court undetermined] for survey of road. Case includes rejoinder, plea, replication, extract of records, declaration, and writ.
    - Samuel Hindman vs. William Duer: Debt, 1775 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Case includes narratio and notice of bail.
    - Uriah Hobbs [Hubbs] vs. Platt Veal and Lemuel Weeks, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Case includes narratio.
    - James Hughes vs. John Johnson: Trespass, 1761 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Case includes declarations.
    - John Hunt vs. Nathaniel Underhill and John Williams, 1773 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Trial in Westchester County. Charges defendants with refusing to swear him in as mayor of Westchester. See also The King vs. Underhill. Case includes a brief.
    - Patrick Hynes vs. William Caverley [Caverly]: Trespass, assault, and battery, 1765 (Box 4, Folder 4)
      Case includes narratio, replication, note security for costs, and plea.
    - James Jauncey vs. James Haviland: Debt, 1769 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Case includes narratios on bond and oyer.
    - John Jackson Jones vs. John Johnson: Debt, 1760 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Case includes narratio. See also John Tabor Kempe's list of sheriff's fees for various cases, 1759-1760.
    - John Shatford Jones vs. Thomas Fisher, 1773 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Manuel Josephson vs. Sampson Simson: Slander, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 5)
      Case includes deposition, brief, replication, plea, narratio, trial notes, notices, list of witnesses, notes, and list of jurors.
    - David Keech vs. John Richards: Assault and battery, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Archibald Kennedy vs. John Schuyler, executor of Adoniah Schuyler, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      See also John Tabor Kempe to Mr. Walter [undated] and Captain Kennedy to Cortlandt and Skinner, dated November 1771. Case includes power of attorney, articles of agreement, award, warrant, notes, and arbitration bond.
    - John Phillips, admin of Christopher Kilby vs. William McAdam: Debt, 1774-1775 (Box 4, Folder 6)
      Case filed under Kilby. Case includes account, notice of trial, brief, narratio, list of jurors, affidavit, replication, notice of motion for struck jury, notice of special bail, and plea.
    - John Tabor Kempe vs. James Abeel: Debt, 1773-1775 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Case includes notice of taxing costs, narratio, oyer, and costs.
    - [Peter Quiet ex dem] John Tabor Kempe and others vs. Jeremiah French, 1771 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Trial in Albany County. See also [Peter Quiet ex dem] John Tabor Kempe vs. Gideon Brunson, on same sheet. Case includes notes.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] John Tabor Kempe, James Duane, and Walter Rutherford vs. [John Stiles] Eliakim [Eliacom] Weller [Walton] [Wallor]: Ejectment, 1769-1771 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Trial in Albany County. Brief notes also on sheet with [James Jackson ex dem] John Tabor Kempe vs. Gideon Brunson. Case includes notice of trial, notice of stiking jury, subpeonas, rule and plea, declaration, and jury list.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] John Tabor Kempe, James Duane, and Walter Rutherfurd vs. [John Stiles] Samuel Rose: Ejectment, 1770 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Trial in Albany County. Case includes costs, jury list, notice of trial, declaration, rule and plea, and brief.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] John Tabor Kempe, James Duane, and Walter Rutherford vs. [John Stiles] Thomas French: Ejectment, 1771 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Trial in Albany County and includes a declaration.
    - John Tabor Kempe on behalf of the King vs. Andrew Lardner, 1772 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Case includes notice and deposition.
    - John Tabor Kempe vs. Jonathan Fish, 1774 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Case includes notice of exception to bail, notice of bail, and notes.
    - [Peter Quiet et dem] John Tabor Kempe and others vs. Gideon Brunson: Ejectment, 1771 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Trial in Albany County. On the same sheet as [James Jackson et dem] John Tabor Kempe vs. Eliakim Weller and [Peter Quiet ex dem] John Tabor Kempe vs. Jeremiah French. Case includes notes.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] Bernardus La Grange [Lagrange] [Le Grange] vs. Catherine Van Renselaer and Robert Freeman: Ejectment, 1773-1774 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      See also Catherine Van Renselaer vs. Simon J. Veeder et al. and Philip Livingston vs. Simon Veeder. Also see correspondence between Peter Yates to John Tabor Kempe, 25 January, 1774; Barnard Lagrange to John Tabor Kempe, 21 February, 1774; John Tabor Kempe to Le Grange, 17 February, 1774; and John Tabor Kempe to Egbert Dumond, 21 May, 1774. Case includes subpeona, rule and plea,draft of venire, agreement, notes, sketch of title, notice for balloting jury, notes of authorities, narratio, notice of motion for foreign jury and view, and subpeona (draft).
    - James Leadbetter vs. George Harison: Slander, 1771 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      See also Leadbetter vs. Harison, Nicholls, and Folliott in Chancery. Case includes affidavit, trial notes, notice of trial, plea, brief, and narratio.
    - Robert Leake [Lake] vs. William Chase [Chace] [Chease]: Assault, 1763 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      See also Robert and Mary Scott vs. William Chase. See correspondence between John Tabor Kempe and Robert Leake and a letter from Silvester to John Tabor Kempe, 30 January, 1762. Case includes narratio, replication, plea, and notice of trial.
    - Cornelius Lowler vs. Martin Pendergast, Joseph Fitzpatrick, and Edward Loghnane: Trespass, assault, and battery, 1762-1763 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      Two trials, same incident. Documents are filed together. Case includes notice of special bail, plea, declaration, replication, roll, and notice of trial.
    - Leffert Lefferts vs. Cornelius Vandervoort [Van Der Voort] and Elizabeth Bennet: Slander, assault, and battery, 1775 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Trial in Kings County. See also Cornelius Van Der Voort [Vandervoort] vs. Leffert Lefferts in Supreme Court Judicature. Case includes statement of case, notice of trial, brief, replication, narratio, plea, and notes.
    - Hayman Levy [Levi] vs. Barack [Barak] [Barrak] Hays [Hayes]: Debt, 1772-1773 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      Case includes costs, notice of bail, affidavit, plea, costs, brief, trial notes, narr, notice of trial, accounts, and replication.
    - Philip Livingston, admr of Jeremiah Van Rensselaer vs. Simon Johannes Veeder, executor of Johannes Simonse Veeder: Trespass, 1770-1774 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      See correspondence from John Glen to John Tabor Kempe, 12 November 1770, and Kempe to Robert Yates, 8 February, 1774. Case includes rule to plead, opinions, copy of deed, oyer of lease, narratio, plea, writ, and opinion.
    - Peter Lockwood vs. Peter Powers, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - James McClaughry, executor of Alexander Clinton vs. Abraham Roosa: Debt, 1768 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case in Ulster County. Includes narratio and bond. The case is on John Tabor Kempe's list of fees for Supreme Court of Judicature, 1767.
    - James McEvers, Theophilact Bache, John Alsop, assignees of Hayman Levy vs. Peter DuBois and Henry Van Schaack, 1767-1769 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case includes notes on insufficiency of affidavit, affidavits, and costs.
    - Phineas McIntosh vs. Isaac Moses: Trespass, 1771 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case includes writ and notice of bail.
    - John McKnight [MacKnight] vs. Andrew Maerschalk [Marschalk]: Assault, 1762 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case includes narratio. On John Tabor Kempe's list of costs for Supreme Court of Judicatue, 1762.
    - Samson Mears vs. Abraham Schenk: Debt, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Levin Milby vs. James Holmes and Gersham Mott, 1767 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      See also Burton Robeinson vs. James Holmes and Gersham Mott. See also correspondence from Holmes and Mott to John Dagworthy, 28 December, 1766; John Dagworthy to John Tabor Kempe, 30 December, 1766. Case includes notice of bail, plea, order, notice of trial, and narratio (draft).
    - Juan [John] Miranda vs. Cornelius Van Ranst and Sarah Van Ranst: Trespass and assault, 1758-1759 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Miranda brings suit for assault ag. Van Ranst; Van Ranst pleas that the suit has no merit as Miranda is his slave; Miranda then claims to be a free man. Case includes demand for plea, affidavits, replication, plea, petitions, order of council, roll, and brief.
    - Israel Moore vs. Jonas Phillips [Philips], 1769 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case includes notes for setting aside judgement and costs. Note also states King vs. Jonas Philips on the same document. See also Phillips vs. Hubbard, Moore, et al in Supreme Court Judicature and letter from Jonas Philips to John Tabor Kempe, 4 January, 1770.
    - Lambert Moore qui tam vs. Six Hogs of Rum, 1768 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case includes judgement roll.
    - Manuel Myers vs. Gregory Springall [Spingall] and John Bolitha [Belitha], 1773 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Case includes affidavit, notice of bail, and narratio.
    - Manuel Myers vs. Joseph Simons, 1775 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Trial in Albany County. Case includes a draft of narratio and a copy of a bond.
    - [James Jackson ex dem] The Mayor of NYC vs. [John Turnout] John Devoor: Ejectment, 1772 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Robert Nugent vs. Hezekiah Pearsal, James Pearsal, and Henry Pearsal [Pearshall], 1762 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      See also correspondence between John Tabor Kempe and Robert Nugent dated 5 April, 1762; 20 July, 1762; and 8 November, 1762. Case includes costs, notice of taxing costs, note of appearance, rule, and account.
    - John Ogden qui tam vs. Edward Allison: Debt, 1767 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Case includes narratio and plea.
    - John Ogden qui tam vs. Thomas Wooley, 1768 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Trial in Dutchess County. Case includes rules, narratio, and plea.
    - John Ogden qui tam vs. Oke Suidam, 1771 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Trial in Ulster County. Case includes plea, rejoinder in demurrer, demurrer, notes, notice of motion, and narratio.
    - Thomas Pennoyer vs. Gilbert Budd, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Trial in Westchester County. Case includes narratio and writ.
    - [John Denn] Frederick Philips vs. [John Turnout] Anne Bernard: Ejectment and trespass, 1769 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Philip Philipse [Phillipse], assignee of William Barret vs. Arent Smith, Cornelius Smith, Harmanus Smith, execrs of Cornelius Smith, deceased, 1772-1773 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      See also correspondence to John Tabor Kempe from Abraham Yates and Peter Van Schaack. Also a letter from Arent Smith, Cornelius Smith, and Harmanus Smith dated 8 May, 1774. Case includes a warrant of attorny, writ, and costs.
    - Jonas Phillips vs. Joshua Hubbard, James Rodgers, John Howell, Samuel Hubbard, and Israel Moore, 1769 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      See also Israel Moore vs. Jonas Phillips in Supreme Court of Judicature. Case includes case, affidavits, certiorari, and subpoena.
    - Charles Prosser vs. Edward Welch [and Margaret Welch], 1760-1761 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      See also Welch vs. Prosser in Supreme Court of Judicature. The two cases are for the same incident with both parties counter suing each other for assault. Both cases are on John Tabor Kempe's agenda in 1760. See letter from John Tabor Kempe to Thomas Smith, dated 17 April, 1761. Case includes narration and release.
    - David Provoost vs. Mary Lush, 1763 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Case includes draft of record in error.
    - David Provoost vs. Falconier Valleau: Trespass, 1772-1773 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Case includes a plea draft, note to plead, and narratio.
    - David Provoost vs. Abraham Lott, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Case includes notice of motion for a foreign jury.
    - David Pryce [Price] vs. Francis Koffler, 1763 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      See correspondence from John Troy to Captain Coffler [Koffler], 19 October, 1762 and John Troy to David Price [Pryce], 20 October, 1762. Case includes declaration and plea.
    - David Pryce vs. Hugh Wallace, 1763 (Box 5, Folder 3)
      See correspondence from John Troy to Captain Coffler [Koffler], 19 October, 1762 and John Troy to David Price [Pryce], 20 October, 1762. Case includes narratio.
    - Garret Rapalje vs. William Faulkner: Debt, 1770-1771 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      See also William Faulkner vs. Garret Rapalje in Supreme Court of Judicature. Case includes narratio, notice of bail, notes, notes of evidence, account, and costs.
    - John Rapalje vs. Jeremiah Brower, 1774-1775 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Trial in Kings County. See also John Rapalje vs. Jacob Sebring. Case includes Note, notice of trial, list of jurors, plea, narratio, notice of motion for having a view, survey, articles of agreement, indenture, rule, affidavit, and panel list.
    - John Rapalje vs. Jacob Sebring: Trespass, 1775 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      See also Rapalje vs. Jeremiah Brower. Case includes notice for having a view, affidavit for having a view, notice for plea, plea, motion for view, narratio, venire, rule, and copy of writ.
    - Robert Richard Randall vs. George Lucam: Trespass, 1772 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Reformed Protestant Dutch Church in Albany, ministers and elders vs. John Bradstreet: Trespass, 1764-1765 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      See also letters from John Tabor Kempe to John Bradstreet. Affidavit of Gisbert Marsolis. Case includes narratio (copy), extracts of Albany charter, statement of court costs, report, notice of trial, land grants (copies), countermand notice of trial, affidavit, notice of motion for elizors, notice of striking jury, and panel of struck jury.
    - Hendrick Remson vs. The Mayor, Alderman and Commonally of the City of New York, 1746 (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Case includes a cope of a paperbook. Case is for "money received of Plaintiff for ferriage of the Goods of others the inhabitants of Brucklyn in the Plaintiff's boat."